Goodbye, Eiji!
Eiji...
I only have eyes for you now.
You're going to get wet, Eiji.
If I just think of it as your tears,
getting soaked by the rain isn't so bad.
I see. So this is where her heart flutters.
All right, check.
Onii-chan, let me borrow some manga.
You're still studying?
The execution of revenge is just like studying.
#4 "Clear and Present Danger"
Don't ever collect such
erroneous information again.
I'm terribly sorry, Aki-sama.
Adagaki Aki...
I'm going to make my revenge a
reality with this next plan.
Rose-eyed Steroid
Hanano Rabuko
All right, that's it for today's classes.
Supplementary Class
All of you who have supplementary
classes, please head over there now.
You have to sit there?
Of course.
Emperor Go-Daigo
Southern Imperial Court (Yoshino)
Three Imperial Regalia of Japan
In this era when the conflict
between the Northern Imperial Court
and the Southern Imperial
Court was intense,
the Southern Court, at one
point, occupied Kyo.
But the Northern Imperial
Court was able to retake Kyo.
Eventually, when Ashikaga
Yoshimitsu was enthroned,
the Northern Imperial Court
continued to get stronger.
They moved their residence
to Kitakoji Muromachi...
Why don't you face forward?
I only have eyes for you now.
So cold!
Maybe I'll have Yoshino
bring me an umbrella.
If I just think of it as your tears,
getting soaked by the rain isn't so bad.
Bye.
Hey, Makabe!
How do you like my love-blooming plan?
I totally nailed it!
Creepy?
"Seriously creepy," to be precise.
W-Wait a sec! Is that what Adagaki said?
I think she said that 24 times today alone.
I'm going to kill that bitch!
I think so too, though.
Listen here. "Rose-eyed Steroid" is a classic!
It's a bible for all maidens!
That's not the problem here.
Pig's Foot, it's time you withdrew a bit.
Huh?
You can't just keep pushing.
Mixing things up is important.
"Mixing things up"?
Next time, you can be as
cold as possible to her.
I have returned.
You're late. How long does it take
you to go to the convenience store?
I'm very sorry. There was a stray cat.
As if I care about that.
Come on, give it here.
Well, it's true that
Huh?
That has nothing to do
with me anymore.
After Eiji started
acting cold to me,
I was finally able to realize
my true feelings...
the heroine realizing how she really
feels when the hero is cold to her
is the most standard of tropes.
But what happens if I'm cold to
her and she hates me even more?
I feel as if I've finally rid myself
of one of those annoying flies.
It's quite a relief.
Hey, Adagaki-sa—
Creepy.
Crap! I almost started
talking to her reflexively!
As Master said, mixing
things up is important.
H-Hey...
I did it! I actually did it!
I ignored the Cruel Princess!
I might have also destroyed
all the effort and likability
that I've built up to this point.
But the die is cast.
Supplementary Class
Yo, Makabe!
Are you sitting here, Masamune-kun?
Yeah. Is this seat available?
Oh, yeah. Have a seat.
Yay!
See you later, Makabe-kun!
See you tomorrow.
Bye-bye!
Well, how about it?
You miss me like crazy now, don't you?
I-It backfired?! Hold up!
Are you telling me not to
try to get close yet, Master?
What if it's always going
to be like this now?
Was I actually some
background character?
Makabe.
She suddenly ambushed me head-on?!
I need to talk to you.
If you're going to say that at this
point, wouldn't it usually...
Um, um,
I have something to talk
to you about, Makabe-kun...
...be more like that?!
Instead of being all shy, she's totally
in angry Cruel Princess mode!
M-Maybe some other time.
Wait a second!
Ow! What the hell?
Don't give me that! That's my line!
Let go of me!
No!
Are you stupid?! Are you absolutely stupid?!
What are you even trying to do?!
S-Stop! Stop it...
What is this?
I won't stop! What's going on?!
Stupid, stupid, stupid!
It's like I'm in a brawl or getting
threatened by some thug!
Does this mean I'll never be able to
be like the protagonist in a shojo manga?
Why are you ignoring me?
I don't know what I'm supposed to do.
Wh-Whoa...
This is totally
her being all shy, right?!
No, wait, wait. You can't
fall for a shy Adagaki Aki.
You're amazing, Master! It went
just like you said it would!
Now I'm going turn things back around.
You see...
I've been waiting for you
to say that, Adagaki-san.
Wha— You mean it was on purpose?!
You're awful!
A-Awful?
I just received a comment that cut like a knife.
Are you sure this didn't backfire, Master?
No, wait...
She's calling me harsh things like "awful," but...
You're truly awful. I can't believe you.
Even though she's yelling at me,
she doesn't sound prickly,
but actually sounds kind of troubled.
I think this is where I'm
supposed to go out on a limb.
Why would you do something like that?
W-Well, that's because I lik—
What is there to like about me?
Huh?
My sign was ranked #1 in today's horoscope.
You want me to state the reasons?
Wow, lucky!
You have a pretty face, but you hate guys.
Pudding
Prince
You have a great body,
but you're a gluttonous fiend.
You're smart, but you're oblivious.
And you ask what there is to like
about such a Cruel Princess?
I hadn't really thought about it! Teehee!
Yeah, I probably shouldn't say that.
Wh-What is there?
E-Everything! Everything about you!
Wh-What's that supposed to mean?
You're absolutely the best!
Oops, sorry! Just remembered
I have somewhere I need to be!
Makabe!
Uh, Masamune-kun?! Why are you running away?
You actually managed to get that
much of a reaction out of her!
What are you going to do after this?
I have no idea!
Come on, Master!
Are you stupid?
Don't call me stupid!
I didn't consider that you hadn't
even thought about that.
Don't lose hope in me! That pisses me off!
We need to think of something! Anything!
Come on, give me something that'll make
her heart flutter when she hears it!
I'm not some cat robot.
I know. What if I tell her she's pretty?
No.
Huh? No? Why?!
Don't sigh right there!
A letter's the only way to go.
If I try to say it verbally,
I'll probably flub it up.
Master's ideas are amazing.
What are you doing?
P-Perfect timing.
Listen, would you mind reading this?
It says how I feel right now.
I absolutely despise you.
You seem to have the wrong idea. I'm—
Shut up!
You can't fool me!
I saw through your selfishness
a long time ago!
Hey! Adagaki-san?!
Is something wrong?
Master...
I have no idea what's going on anymore!
She suddenly says she despises
me and runs off like that.
And she's acting totally
different from yesterday.
What the heck is going on?
I thought things were finally
going well yesterday. Damn it!
All right. Leave it to me.
Do you have an idea what's
going on? Tell me, Master!
I just said to leave it to me, didn't I?
Right now, you can't even explain
what you like about Aki-sama.
That means nothing you say
will get through to her.
I-I...
Don't worry. I'll make sure you'll
be able to go out with her.
Is she telling the Pig's
Foot to stay out of it?
Damn it, Makabe Masamune.
Who is this revenge for?
It's for me, isn't it?!
I can't get my revenge if I'm just sitting
here like I'm waiting to be fed.
That's unacceptable!
This is the first time I've skipped class.
A-Am I going to get in trouble?
Hey!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Darn it, Cookie! Come back here!
I can't take it anymore!
Why must I feel so irritated?
This is all...
You're absolutely the best!
Oops, sorry! Just remembered
I have somewhere I need to be!
Makabe!
Hey! You forgot this!
Come on, Master!
"Master"?
I didn't consider that you hadn't
even thought about that.
Don't lose hope in me! That pisses me off!
We need to think of something! Anything!
Come on, give me something that'll make
her heart flutter when she hears it!
What does he mean by "everything"?
I'm not some cat robot.
I bet he's been saying that to
all the girls! That scumbag!
When did he and Yoshino...
After he asked me out on
a date so many times...
I knew it'd end up like this!
Aki-sama.
Why didn't you tell me?
Did you need something?
I can decide for myself whether
I want to go to class.
You can go back to class.
Aki-sama, I was meeting
with Makabe Masamune-kun.
He needed someone to talk to.
Oh? And?
He emailed and called me, too.
So what?
It doesn't matter to me that
you and Makabe are close.
Are you sad?
That's inconceivable. Why would I
be sad over that cocky narcissist?
Is that really all?
Honestly, this girl...
She's usually so slow, but somehow,
she's always so sharp when
it comes to things like this.
Th-That's inconceivable!
I would never be sad over a boy.
That'll never happen again.
Because there's something that
I still believe in very strongly.
Boys are all just liars!
They're selfish and do whatever
they want, and in the end...
They act like nothing ever happened.
That might be true.
Yes, it is. That's why...
It's inconceivable that
I would ever like a boy.
I won't be sad about the fact
that Makabe Masamune was
meeting with Yoshino without my knowledge,
let alone fall in love with him.
There's no doubt about it!
It's okay, Aki-sama.
He only has eyes for you.
You like him too, don't you?
Th-Th-That's not true.
Of course that's not true!
Wait a second, Yoshino!
Ugh, where did she go?
Mommy, I'm hungry!
Why am I so irritated? I'm...
awful.
I'm such a terrible person.
I've always hurt other people
so I wouldn't get hurt.
If it means never having
to go through that again,
I'd rather be hated and have people
keep their distance from me.
That's why I did everything I've done.
Why am I remembering the past?
I don't know.
I don't know if he actually likes me.
And I...
Stop!
I thought I finally found you and then...
What the hell were you
thinking?! The light was red!
I-It's not like it matters to you!
Be serious!
Of course that's not true! I don't
know what I'd do without you!
Is that really all?
A-Adagaki-san? Sorry,
I might've said too much.
I...
I'm so terribly sorry! Are you all right?
Were you hurt?
No, I'm fine.
I see. Thank goodness.
My Lord...
Our Father, who art in heaven...
I can't believe it.
I can't believe that this
could happen here.
I've been longing to see you.
Who the hell is this?!